Mitch Raznick

Full-Stack Developer

Brooklyn, NY | 402-980-4919 | mraznick@gmail.com

About me:

I'm a creative-thinking, problem-solving, and impact-driven full-stack developer with over six years of sales experience. I can bring efficiency and culture to a team by applying creative approaches to the toughest challenges with effective communication and delivery skills.

Coding Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Python

Environments, Programs, and Frameworks: NodeJS, Mongoose, MongoDB, Express, Axios, Django

Portfolio | GitHub

Projects:

Cowboy Bebop Tabbed Website

- Independently built from scratch using React, Axios, and CSS, sourcing all images and content were sourced from the Kitsu API.
- Displays synopsis, art gallery, series info, and episode description of one of the most popular anime series of all-time.

Directory of Astronauts

- Independently built a simplified version of NASA's API using Mongoose, Express, and Axios.
- Includes full CRUD functionality with RESTful routes.

Virtual Art Institute of Chicago

- Full-stack group project that serves as an online-based museum using data from the Art Institute of Chicago's public API.
- My role was to code the front-end logic using React., including all API calls, forms, and user registration/login.
- Back end repo (with full Read Me doc, written by me) can be found here.

the reper (with ran reduced to constitution of me)

Professional Experience:

BUTTERFLYMX| SALES DIRECTOR| JAN 2022 - MAY 2022

- Identified and prospected 50+ opportunities in the multi-family real estate industry per day
- Built Hubspot outreach sequences to make 30+ cold calls and 50+ cold emails per day
- Created a sales deck and software demo of our product, presenting 3-6 times daily to audiences of 1-10 prospects
- Generated around \$10K in ARR in my first quarter through my Salesforce pipeline

HOMEADVISOR/ANGI | JUNE 2016 - DEC 2021

INSIDE SALES MANAGER | JULY 2018 - DEC 2021

- Trained, developed, and coached a team of 10-14 reps for B2B sales via cold calls, including weekly 1:1s, live coaching on calls, writing unique scripts and one-sheets, and teaching pipeline management best practices
- Used datamining software to generate thousands of leads per week to keep rep pipelines built-up
- Hosted workshops to share various sales theories, strategies, and creative approaches to company initiatives
- Achieved highest revenue in the org for 03 2021
- Tracked and reported weekly sales performance, productivity, and metrics. Applied the data to predict trends and proactively apply solutions for improving performance

SENIOR ONLINE MARKETING CONSULTANT | JUNE 2016 - JULY 2018

Independently conducted inside sales for lead generation and online advertising to contracting companies

- Served as a team lead assisting newer reps in sales methods, strategies, and pipeline management
- Research target audiences, communication strategies, pitching methods, and product knowledge
- Analyze user data to adjust accounts for productivity

Education:

- General Assembly Cohort of August 2022: Software Engineering Immersive Course | NYC
 - o Completed over 400 hours of coding, amounting to 25 assignments and 10 projects over 13 weeks
 - o Built fully operating applications and databases both independently and as part of a team
- The University of Kansas Class of 2015: BS in journalism, minor in film & media studies | Lawrence, KS
- Danish Institute of Study Abroad | Copenhagen, DK